### Contact

s.munajeter@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/s-munajeter-21565a157 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Healthcare Management Patient Safety Acute Care

### Certifications

Nurse Executive Advanced (NEA-BC)

# S. Muna Jeter

Director of Patient Care Services at Ascension Owings Mills, Maryland

# Summary

Experienced Director Of Patient Services with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Advanced Cardiac Life Support (ACLS), Acute Care, Critical Care Nursing, Healthcare Management, and Patient Safety. Strong healthcare services professional with a MSN focused in Health/Health Care Administration/Management from University of Maryland Baltimore.

# Experience

Ascension

Director of Patient Care Services March 2018 - Present (2 years 4 months)

St. Agnes Hospital

Critical Care Units, Cardiac Cath Lab, Respiratory Therapy, & Sleep Lab

American Heart Association Go Red for Women Executive Leadership Committee March 2020 - Present (4 months)

Baltimore, Maryland, United States

LifeBridge Health
Critical Care & Emergency Services
December 2015 - March 2018 (2 years 4 months)
Baltimore, Maryland Area

University of Maryland Medical Center Midtown Campus Clinical Manager September 2013 - December 2015 (2 years 4 months)

Baltimore, Maryland Area

## Education

University of Maryland Baltimore

MSN, Health/Health Care Administration/Management · (2005 - 2008)

Stevenson University
Bachelor of Science - BS, Nursing · (1996 - 1999)

University of Michigan-Flint
Student , Dual Executive DNP & MBA